A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, Accession 2013:082, SG 2 FA1135
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, Accession 2013:082, SG 2
2002-2012
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA1135
16.43 Cubic Feet 42 letter document boxes, 1 legal box.
Arrangement
As received.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Scope and Contents
Primaily consists of grant administration records as well as budgets, reports, proposals, planning documents, meeting records, and program plans.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Commonwealth Fund archive was donated to RAC in 1985. Accretions to the collection continue on an ongoing basis. This material was transferred to the Archive Center in 2013.
- Manhattan Retirement Foundation/Shields, #20040413, 2003-2007 (Box 1, Folder 1-5, Box 2, Folder 6-7)
  - Steve Shields Meadowlark, 2005 July 7; 2013:082:001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Household Matters: A Good Life 'Round the Clock, 2013:082:002 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Harris Interactive Inc./Peugh, #20060486, 2006-2008 (Box 2, Folder 8-10, Box 3, Folder 11-15, Box 4, Folder 16)
- Health Research, Inc./Barhydt, #20050593, 2005-2008 (Box 4, Folder 17-21, Box 5, Folder 22-23)
- Issues Research, Inc./McCarthy, #20090098, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 24-25)
- Academy Health/Martinez-Vidal, #20070231, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 26-27)
- Institute for Family Health/Calman, #20060565, 2006-2008 (Box 6, Folder 28-29)
- The George Washington University/Shin, #20090041, 2008-2010 (Box 6, Folder 30-32)
- The Urban Institute/Bovbjerg, #20080121, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 33-34)
- American Health Quality/Deutsch, #20040810, 2002-2005 (Box 7, Folder 35-37)
  - A Tale of Transformation: 4 Stages to Tell the Story, 2013:082:003 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- University of South Florida/Hyer, #20050582, 2004-2006 (Box 8, Folder 38-43)
- League 1199 SEIU Training and Upgrading Fund/King and Bishop, #20060013, 2005-2010 (Box 9, Folder 44-47)
  - 1199 SEIU Continuing Care Leadership Coalition Quality Care Committee, 2013:082:004 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Brandeis University/Altman, #20080365, 2008-2009 (Box 9, Folder 48-49)
  - The 16th Annual Princeton Conference May 20-21, 2009, 2013:082:005 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Southern Illinois University/Kapp, #20070464, 2007-2009 (Box 10, Folder 50-51)
- University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee/Weisman, #20060717, 2006-2010 (Box 10, Folder 52-53)
- The Regents of the University of California/Estes, #20030247, 2002-2005 (Box 10, Folder 54-56, Box 11, Folder 57-62)
  - The Gerontologist vol 47, no. 3 June 2007, 2013.082.009 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- University of North Texas/Yeatts, #20031440, 2003-2007 (Box 12, Folder 63-67)
  - Journal of Aging and Health Vol 22 no. 6 Sept 2010, September 2010; 2013:082:006 (Box 12, Folder 64)
- Institute for Family-Centered Care/Johnson, #20070552 (Box 13, Folder 68-69)
- Louisiana Public Health Institute/Williams, #20070756, 2007-2008 (Box 13, Folder 70)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance/Schoole, #20070428, 2006-2008 (Box 13, Folder 71-73)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance/Scholle, #20050372 (Box 14, Folder 74-75)
- Pacific Business Group on Health/von Glahn, #20070067, 2005-2007 (Box 14, Folder 76-79)
- Trustees of Darthmouth College/Wasson, #20060400 (Box 15, Folder 80-84)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College/Reede, #20040678, 2004-2007 (Box 15, Folder 85, Box 16, Folder 86-87)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College/Reede, #20060649, 2006-2008 (Box 16, Folder 88-89)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College/Reede, #20070520, 2007-2009 (Box 16, Folder 90, Box 17, Folder 91-94)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Folders 93 and 94 are restriced from research - contains personal information.
- President and Fellows of Harvard College/Reede, #20080381, 2008-2010 (Box 17, Folder 95, Box 18, Folder 96)
- Regents of the University of California/Mukamel, #20050687, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 97-98)
  - The Journals of Gerontology, vol 62b, no 4 July 2007, 2013.082.007 (Box 18, Folder 98)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College/Stevenson, #20070005, 2006-2008 (Box 18, Folder 99-100)
- University of North Texas/Yeatts, #20020407 (Box 19, Folder 101-106)
- Health Management Associates, Inc./Smith, #20080304, 2008-2009 (Box 20, Folder 107-108)
- Children's Hospital Medical Center/Simpson, #20090494, 2009-2010 (Box 20, Folder 109-110)
- Center for Health Policy Development/Rosenthal, #20090686 (Box 20, Folder 111)
- Wayne State University/Stanton, #20060643 (Box 20, Folder 112-113)
  - IBS-CTI, 2013:082:010 (Box 20, Folder 113)
- Harris Interactive, Inc./Peugh, #20090382 (Box 21, Folder 114-116)
- Arizona State University/Melnyk, #20070706, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 117-118)
- Massachusetts General Hospital/Weissman, #20020727, 2002-2004 (Box 22, Folder 119-123)
- Princeton Survey Research Associates/McIntosh, #20050365 (Box 23, Folder 124-125)
- Health Technology Center/Tunis, #20070118, 2007-2009 (Box 23, Folder 126-129, Box 24, Folder 130)
  Folder 130 is closed to research - contains personal information.
- Trustees of Dartmouth College/Fisher, #20070129, 2007-2009 (Box 24, Folder 131-132)
- Project HOPE/Wilensky, #20070119, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 133)
- Massachusetts General Hospital/Weissman, #20060408, 2006-2009 (Box 25, Folder 134-138)
- Research Triangle Institute/Trisolini, #20060506 (Box 26, Folder 139-141)
- Vermont State Legislature/Hester, #20110108, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 142)
- Vermont State Legislature/Hester, #20090669 (Box 26, Folder 143)
- AcademyHealth/Helms, #20100513, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 144)
- AcademyHealth/Helms, #20100089, 2009-2010 (Box 26, Folder 145)
- Dobson Da Vanzo & Associates, LLC/Dobson, #20090497, 2009-2010 (Box 27, Folder 146-147)
- Pacific Business Group on Health/Delbanco, #20110281, 2010-2011 (Box 27, Folder 148)
- Harvard Medical School, Jain, #20031443 (Box 27, Folder 149)
- National Quality Forum, Kenneth Kizer, #20031306 (Box 27, Folder 150)
- Pioneer Network in Culture Change/Kantor, #20080354, 2007-2009 (Box 27, Folder 151, Box 28, Folder 152-154)
  - Advocating a New Old Age: A Pioneer Network Call to Actions, 2013:082:008 (Box 27, Folder 151)
- Pioneer Network in Culture Change/Kantor, #20070511, 2007-2008 (Box 28, Folder 155-156, Box 29, Folder 157-160)
- Pioneer Network/Fagan, #20060373, 2005-2007 (Box 29, Folder 161, Box 30, Folder 162-163)
- Pioneer Network/Fagan, #20050333, 2005-2006 (Box 30, Folder 164-166, Box 31, Folder 167-168)
- Brown University/Edward Miller, #20090426, 2009-2010 (Box 31, Folder 169-172)
- Brown University/Mor, #20060606, 2005-2007 (Box 32, Folder 173-178, Box 33, Folder 179-181)
- American College of Healthcare Administrators/Grachek, #20080393, 2007-2010 (Box 33, Folder 182-184)
- Pioneer Network/Elliot, #20110065, 2010-2011 (Box 34, Folder 185)
- Green House, VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11750)
  Access copy currently unavailable. Please see a RAC archivist for further instruction.
- Northwestern University/Emanuel, #20060035, 2005-2006 (Box 34, Folder 186-188)
- University of North Carolina/Zimmerman, #20100596 (Box 34, Folder 189-190)
- Psychosocial Care in Nursing Homes: Invitational Conference, April 4-5, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 191-192)
- University of Massachusetts/Miller, #2011033, 2011-2012 (Box 35, Folder 193-195)
- Urban Institute/Long, #20080227 (Box 36, Folder 196-197)
- Brookings Institution/McKethan, #20080223 (Box 36, Folder 198)
- Lewin Group/McKethan, #20070337 (Box 36, Folder 199-201)
- University of Pittsburgh/Castle, #20070403, 2007-2010 (Box 37, Folder 202-204)
- LeadingAge/Minnix, #20080355, 2008-2010 (Box 37, Folder 205-206, Box 38, Folder 207)
  Scope and Contents
  (AAHSA changed new name to LeadingAge)
- American Association of Homes and Services for the Aging/Minnix, #20070546, 2007-2008 (Box 38, Folder 208-211)
  - The Reference Book, 2008 July 1; 2013:002:012 (Box 38, Folder 209)
- American Association of Home and Services for the Aging/Stone, #20070060, 2007-2010 (Box 39, Folder 212-217)
  Folder 214 is restricted from research - contains personal infomation.
- AcademyHealth/Rogal, #20110124, 2010-2011 (Box 40, Folder 218-220)
- AcademyHealth/Simpson, #20120039, 2011-2012 (Box 40, Folder 221)
- AcademyHealth/Rogal, #20090079, 2009-2010 (Box 40, Folder 222-223, Box 41, Folder 224-226)
- University of Pittsburgh/Degenholtz, #20070353 (Box 41, Folder 227-228, Box 42, Folder 229-232)
  Folder 229 is restricted from research - contains personal information.